Guide to the Hollin Hills Civic Association records, 1950-2013
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 5: Design Review, 1956-2010; (Boxes 50-58)
  - Design Review Committee-Burns Files, 1989-1990 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Design Review Announcement of New Buildings, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Design Review Fight, Criticisms, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Design Review Legal Documents, 1958-1983 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Design Review Magazines, 1975-2010 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Design Review Magazines, Clippings, 1951-1967 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Design Review Miscellaneous Records, 1977-2006 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Design Review Papers, 1980-1989 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Design Review Robert Fisher Documents, 1980-1990 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Series 6: News Clippings and Miscellaneous Records, 1951-2012; (Box 1, 58-60)
  This series consists of newspaper and magazine clippings regarding the architecture, people, and events of Hollin Hills. It also contains architecture plans and small maps of the neighborhood layout. The series also holds miscellaneous records as well as real estate advertisements.
  - Architecture, 1970-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Maps, 1955-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1956-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Ads, 1954-2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Magazines, 1960-2005 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings - Architecture, 1951-1990 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings - People, 1965-1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1956-1963 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1990-1999 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1999-2001 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Magazines - Homes, 1975-2010 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles - Homes, 1986-2010 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Parkland, 1967-2004 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Publications Concerning Residences, 1989-2008 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Series 7: House and Garden Tours and Other Events, 1953-2012; (Boxes 60-64)
  This series contains photographs, brochures, publicity information, scripts, and other documents concerning the house and garden tours put on by Hollin Hills residents. It also documents about Hollin Hills resident artists, Fourth of July picnics, and community balls and galas.
  - Gala Invitations, Not Attending, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Homes in Hollin Hills Papers, 2008-2010 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Hollin Hills: An Artistic Legacy Publications, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - An Artistic Legacy: Publicity, 1953-1998 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - An Artistic Legacy: Artists' Vitae A-G, 1949-1999 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - An Artistic Legacy: Artists' Vitae H-Z, 1949-1999 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Artists and Shows, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Artist Photos, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Artist Questionnaires, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Balls, Shows, Entertainment, Picnics, 1957-1963 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Picnic Receipts, 1998-2007 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - 4th of July Picnic, 1990-2004 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - 50th Gala File, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Gala Attendees, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - House Tour, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - House and Garden Tour, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - House Tours, 1967-2008 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - House and Garden Tour, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - House and Garden Tour, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - House and Garden Tour, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - House and Garden Tour Brochures, 1999, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - House and Garden Tour Miscellaneous Info, 1989-2008 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - House and Garden Tour Publications, 1989-2010 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - House and Garden Tour Publicity, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Garden Tour, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Garden Tour Photographs, 1968-2012 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Garden Tour Scripts, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Series 8: Directories, 1950-2012; (Boxes 66-68)
  This series contains directories with lists of Hollin Hill residents' addresses and telephone numbers, as well as miscellaneous publications regarding the community.
  - CAHH Directory, Listings, 1971-1998 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Historical Publications, 1949-1989 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Directories/CAHH, 1950s (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Directories, 1956-1986 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Directories, 1960-1964 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Directories, 1965-1970 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Directories, 1970-1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Directories, 1975-1980 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Directories, 1980-1985 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Directories, 1985-1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Directories, 1990-1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Directories, 1996-1999 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Directories, 2000-2005 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Directories, 2006-2012 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Series 9: Audio and Visual Material, 1970-1999; (Boxes 68-71)
  This series is composed of photographs and photographic slides, cassettes, floppy disks with community information, and VHS tapes of celebrations, flooding, and other events in the community.
  - Photographs, 1990-1998 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Archival Disks Directory, 1970-1980 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Audio/Visual, 1981-1999 (Box 69)
    Treasury, directories, letters, data, bylaws, leases, other data
  - Audio/Visual, 1988-1999 (Box 70)
    Floppy disks, cassettes (meetings, interviews), VHS tapes (anniversaries, garden tours), microreel (minutes)
  - Photographic Slides, 1970-1990 (Box 71)
- Series 10: Oversize, 1959-2009; (Boxes 72-73)
  This series is composed of a ledger, an addendum, and a 50th anniversary book layout. It also contains blueprints regarding neighborhood layout, pool construction, and design review and construction on individual homes.
  - Blueprints, 1950-2009 (Oversize Mapcase)
    Blueprints, 1999-2005
    Blueprints, 1950-1999
    Blueprints, 2000-2003
    Blueprints, 2004-2009
    Pool Blueprints, 1954-1988
    Blueprints-Neighborhood, Paul Springs Drainage, 1968-1987
    Design Review Blueprints Beechwood-Kimbro, 1992-2007
    Design Review Blueprints Martha's, 1997-2005
    Design Review Blueprints Paul Spring-Rippon, 1996-2007
    Design Review Blueprints Rebecca-White Oaks, 2000-2009